{
    "subject": "King_Vidor",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Bud's_Recruit",
    "human_readable": "King Vidor created Bud's Recruit.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.5999055504798889,
            "question": "When was Bud's Recruit released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5530530214309692,
            "question": "Who are the actors in Bud's Recruit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5523354411125183,
            "question": "What genre is Bud's Recruit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5206972360610962,
            "question": "Is Bud's Recruit a movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5181385278701782,
            "question": "What is the name of the film created by King Vidor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5127680897712708,
            "question": "What is the plot of Bud's Recruit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4950510263442993,
            "question": "Who directed the film Bud's Recruit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39551153779029846,
            "question": "Was King Vidor known for any particular style of filmmaking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38694047927856445,
            "question": "Has Bud's Recruit received any critical acclaim?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2680814266204834,
            "question": "What other films has King Vidor directed?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=King Vidor created Bud's Recruit.",
            "html": "yago_21640_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Bud's Recruit received any critical acclaim?",
            "html": "yago_21640_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was King Vidor known for any particular style of filmmaking?",
            "html": "yago_21640_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who directed the film Bud's Recruit?",
            "html": "yago_21640_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21640_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21640_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21640_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21640_158.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21640_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21640_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21640_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21640_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21640_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21640_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that:\n\n* There is no mention of King Vidor creating Bud's Recruit. Instead, it says \"Bud\u2019s Recruit was one of ten short films written and produced by Judge Willis Brown that were directed by King Vidor.\"\n* Therefore, the statement \"King Vidor created Bud's Recruit\" is incorrect.\n\nHere is the response in the requested format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports that King Vidor directed and produced the film \"Bud's Recruit.\" Therefore, the statement \"King Vidor created Bud's Recruit\" is correct."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "the context information clearly states that Bud's Recruit was written and produced by Judge Willis Brown, not King Vidor.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}